[
    { "question" : "ללכת", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/lelechet/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לראות", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/lir'ot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לעשות", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/la'asot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לדבר", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "/ledaber/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לקנות", "answer" : "to buy", "pronunciation" : "/liknot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לקרוא", "answer" : "to read", "pronunciation" : "/likro/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לכתוב", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "/likhtov/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לאהוב", "answer" : "to love", "pronunciation" : "/le'ehov/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להבין", "answer" : "to understand", "pronunciation" : "/lehavin/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לעבוד", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/la'avod/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לשמוע", "answer" : "to hear", "pronunciation" : "/lishmoa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לפתוח", "answer" : "to open", "pronunciation" : "/liftu'ach/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לסגור", "answer" : "to close", "pronunciation" : "/lisgor/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להתחיל", "answer" : "to start", "pronunciation" : "/lehitkhil/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לספר", "answer" : "to tell", "pronunciation" : "/lesaper/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לספק", "answer" : "to supply", "pronunciation" : "/lesapek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להכין", "answer" : "to prepare", "pronunciation" : "/lehakhin/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לחכות", "answer" : "to wait", "pronunciation" : "/lekhakot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לשאול", "answer" : "to ask", "pronunciation" : "/lish'ol/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להיראות", "answer" : "to appear", "pronunciation" : "/lehir'ot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לכבות", "answer" : "to turn off", "pronunciation" : "/likvot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להפסיק", "answer" : "to stop", "pronunciation" : "/lehafsik/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לבוא", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "/lavo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לשים", "answer" : "to put", "pronunciation" : "/lesim/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להישאר", "answer" : "to stay", "pronunciation" : "/lehis'arer/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להגיד", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "/lehagid/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להגיע", "answer" : "to arrive", "pronunciation" : "/lehegi'a/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להוסיף", "answer" : "to add", "pronunciation" : "/lehosif/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לשנות", "answer" : "to change", "pronunciation" : "/leshannot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להצטער", "answer" : "to be sorry", "pronunciation" : "/lehit'ater/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להתראות", "answer" : "to see you", "pronunciation" : "/lehit'ra'ot/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לקבל", "answer" : "to receive", "pronunciation" : "/likabel/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "לחפש", "answer" : "to search", "pronunciation" : "/lekhapes/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "למצוא", "answer" : "to find", "pronunciation" : "/limtzo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להביא", "answer" : "to bring", "pronunciation" : "/lehavi/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להפוך", "answer" : "to reverse", "pronunciation" : "/lehafoch/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "להפגש", "answer" : "to meet", "pronunciation" : "/lehipagesh/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "בית", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "/bayit/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "אדם", "answer" : "person", "pronunciation" : "/adam/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ילד", "answer" : "child", "pronunciation" : "/yeled/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "אישה", "answer" : "woman", "pronunciation" : "/isha/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "גבר", "answer" : "man", "pronunciation" : "/gaver/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "יום", "answer" : "day", "pronunciation" : "/yom/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "שנה", "answer" : "year", "pronunciation" : "/shana/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "עיר", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/ir/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "כסף", "answer" : "money", "pronunciation" : "/kesef/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "מקום", "answer" : "place", "pronunciation" : "/makom/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "תודה", "answer" : "thank you", "pronunciation" : "/toda/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "שלום", "answer" : "peace", "pronunciation" : "/shalom/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "עבודה", "answer" : "work", "pronunciation" : "/avodah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "אהבה", "answer" : "love", "pronunciation" : "/ahava/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "משפחה", "answer" : "family", "pronunciation" : "/mishpacha/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "חבר", "answer" : "friend", "pronunciation" : "/chaver/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "יד", "answer" : "hand", "pronunciation" : "/yad/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ראש", "answer" : "head", "pronunciation" : "/rosh/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "לב", "answer" : "heart", "pronunciation" : "/lev/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "עין", "answer" : "eye", "pronunciation" : "/ayin/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "אוכל", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "/ochel/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "מים", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "/mayim/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "אוויר", "answer" : "air", "pronunciation" : "/avir/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ישראל", "answer" : "Israel", "pronunciation" : "/Yisrael/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "עברית", "answer" : "Hebrew", "pronunciation" : "/ivrit/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "מדינה", "answer" : "country", "pronunciation" : "/medinah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "מסעדה", "answer" : "restaurant", "pronunciation" : "/mis'ada/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "בנק", "answer" : "bank", "pronunciation" : "/bank/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "תחבורה", "answer" : "transportation", "pronunciation" : "/tachburah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "רחוב", "answer" : "street", "pronunciation" : "/rechov/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "קפה", "answer" : "coffee", "pronunciation" : "/cafe/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "חלון", "answer" : "window", "pronunciation" : "/chalon/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "דלת", "answer" : "door", "pronunciation" : "/delet/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ספר", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "/sefer/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "דף", "answer" : "page", "pronunciation" : "/daf/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "עיתון", "answer" : "newspaper", "pronunciation" : "/iton/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "בגד", "answer" : "clothing", "pronunciation" : "/beged/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "נעליים", "answer" : "shoes", "pronunciation" : "/na'alayim/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "כיס", "answer" : "pocket", "pronunciation" : "/kis/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "רכב", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "/rakev/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "אוטובוס", "answer" : "bus", "pronunciation" : "/otobus/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "כרטיס", "answer" : "ticket", "pronunciation" : "/kartis/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "שעון", "answer" : "watch", "pronunciation" : "/shaon/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "בית ספר", "answer" : "school", "pronunciation" : "/beit sefer/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "מחשב", "answer" : "computer", "pronunciation" : "/makhshav/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "טלפון", "answer" : "telephone", "pronunciation" : "/telephone/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "מפתח", "answer" : "key", "pronunciation" : "/miftach/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "כרטיס אשראי", "answer" : "credit card", "pronunciation" : "/kartis ashrai/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "טוב", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/tov/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "רע", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "/ra/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ישן", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "/yashan/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "חדש", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "/chadash/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "כבד", "answer" : "heavy", "pronunciation" : "/kaved/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "קל", "answer" : "light", "pronunciation" : "/kal/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "רחב", "answer" : "wide", "pronunciation" : "/rachav/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "צר", "answer" : "narrow", "pronunciation" : "/tzar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ארוך", "answer" : "long", "pronunciation" : "/aruch/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "קצר", "answer" : "short", "pronunciation" : "/katzar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "יפה", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/yafe/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "מכוער", "answer" : "ugly", "pronunciation" : "/meko'ar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "חם", "answer" : "hot", "pronunciation" : "/cham/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "קר", "answer" : "cold", "pronunciation" : "/kar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "קרוב", "answer" : "close", "pronunciation" : "/karov/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "רחוק", "answer" : "far", "pronunciation" : "/rachok/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "נמוך", "answer" : "low", "pronunciation" : "/namuch/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "גבוה", "answer" : "high", "pronunciation" : "/gavoha/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "עגול", "answer" : "round", "pronunciation" : "/agol/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "מרובע", "answer" : "square", "pronunciation" : "/meruba/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ים", "answer" : "sea", "pronunciation" : "/yam/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "הר", "answer" : "mountain", "pronunciation" : "/har/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "רחוב", "answer" : "street", "pronunciation" : "/rechov/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ישר", "answer" : "straight", "pronunciation" : "/yashar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "עגל", "answer" : "round", "pronunciation" : "/egel/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "חד", "answer" : "sharp", "pronunciation" : "/chad/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "כהה", "answer" : "dark", "pronunciation" : "/kohe/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "בהיר", "answer" : "bright", "pronunciation" : "/bahir/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "יבש", "answer" : "dry", "pronunciation" : "/yavesh/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "רטוב", "answer" : "wet", "pronunciation" : "/ratuv/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "שמנמן", "answer" : "fatty", "pronunciation" : "/shmanman/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "דק", "answer" : "thin", "pronunciation" : "/dak/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "עצמאי", "answer" : "independent", "pronunciation" : "/atzmai/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "תקין", "answer" : "correct", "pronunciation" : "/takin/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "שגוי", "answer" : "wrong", "pronunciation" : "/shagui/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "יכול", "answer" : "able", "pronunciation" : "/yachol/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "חסר", "answer" : "lacking", "pronunciation" : "/chasar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "מלא", "answer" : "full", "pronunciation" : "/male/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ריק", "answer" : "empty", "pronunciation" : "/rik/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "נכון", "answer" : "right", "pronunciation" : "/nachon/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "שמאל", "answer" : "left", "pronunciation" : "/smol/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ימין", "answer" : "right", "pronunciation" : "/yamin/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "מהיר", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "/mahir/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "איטי", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "/iti/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "חמוד", "answer" : "cute", "pronunciation" : "/chamud/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "מתוק", "answer" : "sweet", "pronunciation" : "/matok/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "מר", "answer" : "bitter", "pronunciation" : "/mar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "עגול", "answer" : "round", "pronunciation" : "/agol/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "מרובע", "answer" : "square", "pronunciation" : "/meruba/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "עץ", "answer" : "tree", "pronunciation" : "/etz/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "כאן", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/kan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "שם", "answer" : "there", "pronunciation" : "/sham/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "עכשיו", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "/achshav/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "תמיד", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "/tamid/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מאוחר", "answer" : "late", "pronunciation" : "/me'uchar/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מוקדם", "answer" : "early", "pronunciation" : "/mukdam/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "בקרוב", "answer" : "soon", "pronunciation" : "/bekarov/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "עדיין", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/adain/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "יחד", "answer" : "together", "pronunciation" : "/yachad/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "לבד", "answer" : "alone", "pronunciation" : "/levad/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ממש", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "/mamesh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "אולי", "answer" : "maybe", "pronunciation" : "/ulai/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "כמעט", "answer" : "almost", "pronunciation" : "/k'ma'at/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "רק", "answer" : "only", "pronunciation" : "/rak/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ממש", "answer" : "very", "pronunciation" : "/mamash/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "אולי", "answer" : "perhaps", "pronunciation" : "/ulai/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מסיבה", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/mesiba/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "כן", "answer" : "yes", "pronunciation" : "/ken/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "לא", "answer" : "no", "pronunciation" : "/lo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מעט", "answer" : "a little", "pronunciation" : "/me'at/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "הרבה", "answer" : "a lot", "pronunciation" : "/harbe/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "יותר", "answer" : "more", "pronunciation" : "/yoter/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "פחות", "answer" : "less", "pronunciation" : "/pachot/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "כאן", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/kan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "שם", "answer" : "there", "pronunciation" : "/sham/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "עכשיו", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "/achshav/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "תמיד", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "/tamid/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מאוחר", "answer" : "late", "pronunciation" : "/me'uchar/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מוקדם", "answer" : "early", "pronunciation" : "/mukdam/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "בקרוב", "answer" : "soon", "pronunciation" : "/bekarov/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "עדיין", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/adain/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "יחד", "answer" : "together", "pronunciation" : "/yachad/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "לבד", "answer" : "alone", "pronunciation" : "/levad/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ממש", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "/mamesh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "אולי", "answer" : "maybe", "pronunciation" : "/ulai/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "כמעט", "answer" : "almost", "pronunciation" : "/k'ma'at/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "רק", "answer" : "only", "pronunciation" : "/rak/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ממש", "answer" : "very", "pronunciation" : "/mamash/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "אולי", "answer" : "perhaps", "pronunciation" : "/ulai/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מסיבה", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/mesiba/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "כן", "answer" : "yes", "pronunciation" : "/ken/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "לא", "answer" : "no", "pronunciation" : "/lo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "מעט", "answer" : "a little", "pronunciation" : "/me'at/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "הרבה", "answer" : "a lot", "pronunciation" : "/harbe/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "יותר", "answer" : "more", "pronunciation" : "/yoter/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "פחות", "answer" : "less", "pronunciation" : "/pachot/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "בכלל", "answer" : "at all", "pronunciation" : "/beklal/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "באמת", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "/be'emet/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "כאן", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/kan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ו", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "/ve/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "או", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "/o/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אם", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "/im/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "כי", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אך", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "/ach/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "כמו", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/kmo/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "כש", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/k'she/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "עם", "answer" : "with", "pronunciation" : "/im/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "למען", "answer" : "in order to", "pronunciation" : "/lema'an/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אחרי", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/acharei/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "לפני", "answer" : "before", "pronunciation" : "/lifnei/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "כדי", "answer" : "in order to", "pronunciation" : "/k'dei/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "יעד", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/ya'ad/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אז", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/az/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "כמובן", "answer" : "of course", "pronunciation" : "/k'muvan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "בכל זאת", "answer" : "nevertheless", "pronunciation" : "/b'kol zot/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "בגלל", "answer" : "because of", "pronunciation" : "/biglal/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "כשם ש", "answer" : "as", "pronunciation" : "/k'shem she/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "מאחר", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/me'achar/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "בעוד", "answer" : "while", "pronunciation" : "/be'od/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אפילו", "answer" : "even", "pronunciation" : "/afilo/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "במקום", "answer" : "instead of", "pronunciation" : "/b'makom/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "בגלל זה", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/biglal ze/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אין ספק", "answer" : "no doubt", "pronunciation" : "/ein sefek/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אפשר", "answer" : "it's possible", "pronunciation" : "/efshar/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "עד ש", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/ad she/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "עדיין", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/adain/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אולם", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/ulam/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "גם", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "/gam/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "עם זאת", "answer" : "nevertheless", "pronunciation" : "/im zot/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אפילו", "answer" : "even", "pronunciation" : "/afilo/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "לכן", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/lachen/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "מכיוון ש", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/mikayevan she/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אחרי", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/acharei/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "לפני", "answer" : "before", "pronunciation" : "/lifnei/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "עד", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/ad/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "על כך", "answer" : "about it", "pronunciation" : "/al kach/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "בגלל", "answer" : "because of", "pronunciation" : "/biglal/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "למען", "answer" : "for the sake of", "pronunciation" : "/lema'an/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "בשביל", "answer" : "for the sake of", "pronunciation" : "/b'shvil/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אם כן", "answer" : "if so", "pronunciation" : "/im ken/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "אם לא", "answer" : "if not", "pronunciation" : "/im lo/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "לכן", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/lachen/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "עם זאת", "answer" : "nevertheless", "pronunciation" : "/im zot/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]